See ya
Hi
I'm all in here
Why not get value for me?
She's laughing man, put it in the car
Just follow her
Fuck she wants me to call
Take it
Everyone is very happy to see the beauty of the show
See ya is here
We are here to see how she is doing in the middle of the Haasler
She is doing well in the middle of the Haasler
Before the video starts, I want to thank everyone for support
I only paid 20% of my channel in a month
Now this book is over 25%
I hope you guys have not yet subscribed to my channel
If you have not yet subscribed to my channel, please click on the subscribe button for more videos and videos
You can use a few seconds to click the subscribe button for more videos
In the future, I will start with Dougal Open
In the following video,during some red sculpture, Order Astralıyor
It is the only four
From the beginning, the Astralıyor Event 2,000
als in the haasler
look at that
quote
it's it
what Ju?
九 Polish
I'm so sick
Catch two aces.
Two times.
One time, go with it.
You have no idea.
She just said we must have an egg.
That's so sick.
That is not nice.
No sign.
That is the last one.
That's pretty sick.
I mean, it's such a big swing.
Instead of Dr. P winning,
a 24-hour...
I haven't been to Germany for a long time.
I've been in the jungle for eight or nine days.
I'm not sure how many people eat this.
But if you have a big advantage,
you can put some food in your mouth.
And they will play very well.
This is exciting, guys.
Nituchi is playing a hand.
It's something old, man.
I think I did it.
You ate it, Mr.
Don't worry about it.
Crazy Drew, man.
What a flop for him.
Chop pear and a flush drop.
After the flip,
the big tree of the ship came out of the main cave.
Just like a nice marsh.
He was selling a pair of people to help him.
到了 Sierra,
if he comes in,
because he may have an ice-cream,
then there will be some anti-spatial rules.
After the ball,
the ball will be given to Gao.
Because he is playing,
that's not a problem.
But this ball is not very good.
If you have a short leg,
you still hope that you can play with a-go-k-9.
These are more than high-pitched.
If you have a Queen X,
X0,
your A-s are all bad.
It's not good to have a ball.
It's bad shape.
The ball is again developed.
Very lucky.
She specifically needed a jack that was not a club.
And of course,
what comes in turn?
A jack that's not a club.
They do max it too much.
They know what max it is.
They beat half of it.
I'm a little bit over the max.
How does that happen?
It's still so many games.
Yeah.
Never met like a one-of-a-one.
Now I kind of won't go.
Really?
Yeah.
I'll fucking lose here.
I'm gonna sit here and tell me how.
Three thousand.
I know it's the idea.
Crazy Drew makes the call.
I'm looking for a club.
Ciyah, you're home.
I like this one very much.
Because the one who saw it was a player from the team
was the most important player.
When facing a player from the team,
the main purpose of the game was to get a jack.
Especially in this very young world,
there are many players who can get a jack.
There's no problem with the game.
The team also sent a good response to the team.
They gave him three balls.
Ciyah, you're holding it again.
Next, the next game.
The big number of players who just lost
is getting Aces.
Ciyah is following the team.
Ciyah is in the dressing room.
He can't go to the dressing room.
The team has two teams.
Aces is Ceybye's 800.
There are two people who watch Ciyah.
They think they'll give their own life to the rest of the team.
So I want to get a little help.
I'm going to add that.
The team also took the good performance
and got a good score.
They don't have any problems.
The person who is still alive
took the ball to the pitch.
Aces is following the team.
Aces is going to win.
Ceybye's performance
might be a very bad thing to do.
I don't know what to do.
I can't do that.
We never get away from it.
I'm just a PingGan.
Ceybye is going to win.
DGF is going to win.
$19,860 in the pot.
Here's the river.
He's going to win.
And he just played the big tree.
I don't need to pick up the tree.
This is only a small village.
Oyin.
This might be a small village.
Hey, Ceybye is at home.
There's nothing to lose here.
I don't know.
Ceybye is going to win.
I mean, he's shorter than this.
Yeah, he doesn't have any more.
Uncle is very injured.
I thought he's more than me.
25,000 dollars swing in six hands.
Oh, yeah.
That's magic.
That's magic. I'm done.
Crazy.
Today, we didn't have to worry about playing.
We'll go back to rest.
Unfortunately, we didn't have to worry about playing.
Let's see the next episode.
A-go player.
The next five people.
The other players didn't have three hundred.
So, they have four A-4 and three.
Almost no one has a strong card.
No ASK and ASK, no A-3 and ASK.
A-go already has a strong card.
C-Bat.
We can see that only the black and white players
have a strong middle-ish character.
This player, Bair, is also a player who can be self-conscious.
The previous Live Fight Bike was also a fixed place.
It was very easy.
I love Throughout You game.
Many users reload online.
lived and asked for service's capabilities
while I played taking 一 now and later.
This pouquinho nah nah.
M необходeresly
so they can't neglect them to free one completely.
Also I didn't automatically use the most attractive of the team
I've been usingентly twice for the quality
I asked some people to think they could outsmart instead of Planet Bluff
so when they practice twice
When stepping aside
They willemandue hard fromly
I am AI
I have got some ones for the construction
the characters are well enough
She's on tilt.
Maybe bear is making her a call.
She's blocking.
Nice chance to see her.
She's got King Jack.
What do you have?
Nothing I tell you.
Just follow her.
Fuck she wants me to call.
She's got King Jack bear, so you know it.
She picked up diamonds on the turn, break out on the river.
She's steaming.
Peter just showed her a blow.
Take it.
Yes.
Oh, she's got D.A.
Damn it.
The team really thought about it for a long time.
The second team caught a chicken.
One-five of the top four players, Siyah,
is the main player of a financial crisis.
Before the next game,
if you want to join my team,
you can find the team's team
in the capital of the next game.
Welcome to the new team.
It's going too fast right now.
Siyah is in the second round.
Mindy the dog.
It's a dog game nuisance.
Really?
Okay.
Mia and LeBron.
They were beaten up by three or four people.
They really didn't want to.
The second team was beaten up by Baird.
Siyah was beaten up by three people.
He just three-baked with four-three off.
I'll take it out against the machine.
I'm going to grab my raise.
Ready?
Yeah, pretty much.
Two-colders are going to call him.
Might've been better.
The team was beaten up by three people.
Straight flush draw.
Peter's got bottom pair.
Baird you has withed.
Siyah's got half-fault.
Deep and imposition.
Siyah's got a lot of points.
The most action-oriented team was beaten up by Siyah.
They beat both of them.
They gave Siyah a shot.
Another cooler situation.
Five more.
The team was beaten up by five-four-three.
Two people were beaten up by three people.
They probably got the most hit.
She's a little concerned.
She's got six-seven, but not very concerned.
Seven-seven.
Seven-seven more.
Can you get away somehow?
Siyah, go ahead.
Three-three more.
When someone raised this to 17k in the 10-20-40 game.
The rest of the players...
She's silent.
If Peter is here,
he can only get a few thousand.
So he's not only playing in the O-Yin,
but also playing in the O-Yin.
I'm literally tilted because I'm being 100% serious.
You think I'm kidding? I'm zero kidding.
Zero kidding.
Peter plays five.
Oh no.
The last one was pushed.
But there are four more.
$65,000 pot.
Maybe I'm dead.
Siyah...
He's got outspoken.
Nice hands here.
Siyah, you're an animal.
I love it.
That way you can fight in New York really happy.
That one goes to Siyah.
You're getting a really good flight now.
Siyah, Siyah, you're a good flight now.
Let's see if you can see me.
I can't get out.
Siyah, you're going to have a big meal next time.
I'll see you in the next video.
If you like my video, don't forget to subscribe and follow me.
Also, don't forget to click the bell icon to see my other videos.